Alps!
Put your swords up!
We need to stand upright and strong!
Come on!
We stepped on the Mongolians' tail.
They will confront us sooner or later.
All alps needs to be trained!
We'll take more measures.
We'll be more careful in
the border and Karacahisar
which is the passing
route of Mongolians.
My brother must have reached Karacahisar
with Boran Bey and Holofira by now.
I'll inform the other border
posts about your order.
Go ahead, son.
Ride to Akhisar immediately with Gonca.
We've conquered it just
recently so need to fortify it.
While we fight Mongolians...
...we shouldn't give the heathens any chances.
As you order, my Bey.
I need to go finish my preparations, my Bey.
-Stay safe, son.
-Alright, my Bey.
Allah is The Righteous! Allah is Eternal!
-My Bey!
-Allah is The Righteous! Allah is Eternal!
You said I'm no longer a groom.
But it's an honor for
me to take care of Iltutan.
I've just renewed his shoes.
Thanks, Ilbay.
Thank you.
Allah is The Righteous! Allah is Eternal!
-Allah is The Righteous! Allah is Eternal!
Osman Bey.
This hammer you hit on this
anvil for the sake of Allah..
...is the same with the sword our
warriors hits on the chests of heathens.
Well... You need to hit more hammers
to spread Allah's name in the whole world!
And every man in our army
will be swinging a sword!
As you order, my Bey!
We will hit on the anvil until
our wrists are broken, for sure.
Thank you, thnak you.
My Bey.
-Beys have joined the council.
-Okay, Samil.
May your work be easy!
Keep taking measures, Osman.
We'll see if you could show
off when your plan fails!
Aunt.
I almost got caught, aunt.
What's going on little bird?
Meryem, come on.
Meryem, are you alright?
-Are you alright, girl?
-It's fine.
I just lost my balance.
I've become Fatma's friend.
-We're closer to them now.
-Good.
Get much closer.
Gain their trust completely.
It's time.
Why am I just waiting to kill, aunt?
Your being there is useful for me.
Look... Thanks to you...
...I made Mongolians
raise troubles against Kayis.
Yes.
You know what, aunt?
God proved his justice.
They took my family from me.
And God took their daughter.
Bala...
Bala is suffering.
As much as I do.
Not as much as you do.
You have nobody.
She has a husband and children.
They're all with her.
You say Orhan Bey takes measures
against the Mongols in Karacahisar...
...while Alaeddin Bey takes measures against
the Byzantine infidels in Akhisar, my Bey.
-Other measures will be taken, we know, but..
-But?
-What is your concern, Begum Hatun?
-We all know what the Mongols do.
Can we resist such a threat
by only taking precautions?
I don't know, my Bey.
What should we do?
If we are facing such a trouble...
...I say we should unite with powerful
Turkish Beylics like Germiyan and Candar...
...and ensure unity at the frontiers, my Bey.
What should we do, Cerkutay?
My Bey...
Begum Hatun surely knows that...
...Germiyan and Candar
have bowed to the Mongols.
In short, my Bey...
The path Begum Hatun suggests...
...is not the right one.
My Bey, I agree with Cerkutay Bey.
You are a new Bey, Saruca Bey.
He is new...
..but..
..he is talented enough to see the difference...
...between the right and wrong.
We cannot trust those who bow to Mongols...
...and pledge allegiance to them.
Begum Hatun.
If we do as you say...
...then we will be destroyed.
We are alone against Mongols.
But we will always stand tall against those...
...who set their eyes on our state and nation.
Mongols are coming.
Their cursed feet have touched our land again.
Fatma, come on, my daughter,
you and the others go to the tent.
My Bey, Mongol commander Ulugan is coming.
Didn't you notice him as he got in the tribe?
My Bey, they suddenly
appeared in front of the tribe.
Observer Alps didn't see them my Bey.
As we talk about trouble,
trouble arrives at our door.
What will we do now, Osman Bey?
The way they came here...
...will also be their fate.
Osman Bey.
Commander Ulugan.
Don't be mad at your Alps...
...because they couldn't notice our arrival.
After Karesi Bey pledged allegiance...
..we went through the
steep mountains to get here.
Besides..
...if we don't want it..
...let alone you...
...even the eagle in the sky won't notice us.
I swear by...
...everything on the ground...
everything between them.
As long as you and...
...those like you come to our lands...
..we will..
...always be sharp swords.
You are always ready for battle, right, Osman?
But I did not come here to fight...
..I came here to meet you.
I sent my envoy Toygar to you.
But neither did he return, nor did
we receive any message from you.
So I decided to come here and be Osman's guest.
Your envoy, Toygar.
We will talk about that matter.
But first, tell your nokers...
So that you came here as guests...
...they should act accordingly.
Or else..
Let's go inside.
Cerkutay.
Ah Cerkutay.
Now only your name and...
...your blood is Mongol, huh?
Who are you, stranger?
What are you doing here alone?
Don't you hear me?
I am talking to you!
Mongol trouble is at the frontiers.
Go back to your house.
I heard you but..
...why should I go back?
Does Mongols' arrival scare you, brave boy?
I am just worried about you.
Those miserable men will die here.
Who will kill Mongols?
Osman? -Yes, Osman Bey.
Osman Bey and his valiant Alps!
Once they show their heads, they will all die!
You are on a lucky day, brave boy.
Your wish came true.
Commander Ulugan is in Osman's tribe.
He will poison Osman's blood...
...and make his seeing eyes blind.
They will be relieved.
They will think they won't face an attack.
Then..
...Karacahisar will be their grave.
How will we get in there, Commander Altuga?
When night falls, we will break
Karacahisar's defenses through the tunnels.
They won't even sense it.
Who did you torture to learn about
the tunnels, Commander Altuga?
Ulugan has a skilled spy near
Osman who reveals all his weaknesses.
This spy has now given us both Karacahisar...
...and Shahzade Orhan's head.
I am just like you, Osman.
We conquered many castles...
..and cities.
But my tent is the only place I can be happy.
Did you come here just to talk about this?
First, we will drink kimiz, Osman.
I do not become friends with
anyone who I haven't drunk kimiz with.
Wolves can only be friends with wolves.
When I entered your tribe, I noticed something.
Your Alps are getting ready.
Will you fight someone...
...or...
...are you expecting an attack?
Turks live their life by
standing against the cruel...
...as wolves live their life by killing jackals.
We are always ready for battle. Now...
The reason for your visit...
..is your envoy Toyga
I killed him with my sword.
I cut his head off.
So...
...you sent Toygar to Erlik Khan, huh?
And you bravely tell me you killed Toygar...
...right in front of me
without hesitation, Osman?
Cerkutay!
Cerkutay
Your blood still runs fast, huh?
Karacahisar Castle
Alps!
You will increase the security of
Karacahisar and the roads leading to it.
The Mongol threat is at the door.
Lukas dog on the other side.
At all costs, we will defend Karacahisar.
Anyone who shows weakness
or neglects their duty...
...will not be forgiven, know this.
Now everyone to their duties.
As you order my Shahzade.
Boran Bey. -My Shahzade.
I suggest we also increase the watchmen at
the entrances and exits of the tribe fivefold.
-You are right my Shahzade. I'll check.
-Alright.
Orhan.
Let me gather the women
capable of fighting with swords.
Let's stay alert. Besides...
When the cruel Mongols are at our door...
...it does not suit a Kayi
Hatun to sit and wait.
My Holofira..
My beautiful wife.
Every moment, I get to know a new side of you.
I go back to the
first day I saw you...
...my childhood and fall in
love with you all over again.
So your love sometimes fades, Shahzade.
Since you fall in love again.
Did I say that, my moon-faced
one? I said a good thing.
It seems to me that you
want to change the subject.
Is that so?
It seems to me that you might be
the one wanting to change the subject.
Tell me then, what makes you worried?
-Nothing.
-Holofira...
When I look into your eyes..
..I see the concern in them.
Come on, tell me.
My worry is...
...about not being able to
help you enough in your duties.
With one glance of yours...
...you give me the strength to
stand against the whole world.
You've thought well.
Prepare the women.
We will not let those Mongol dogs pass.
Alright.
My little bird gave me great news, Lukas.
She completely gained their trust.
That means we're one
step closer to our goal, Sofia.
Let me give you other good news.
Ulugan has already crossed Osman's border.
Nice.
Osman will never survive this hell.
While dealing with Mongolians,
he will make mistakes.
And his mistakes will be our weapons.
We won't go back to Bursa,
but stay here close to Osman.
You acted impertinently in my council.
As you were a messenger, I tolerated that.
But oppression...
...will never stay unreturned.
Too much bravery...
...will make a man captive.
It seems...
...that was what caused Toygar to die.
The reason why you came here...
You got the answer.
What's your purpose of your stay as a guest?
We sent Toygar as the
messenger for a reason, Osman.
We wanted to show the
tough face of Mongolians first.
I don't know if you're the last
...but you aren't the first
Mongolians I have seen.
I know, Osman.
We came here and believed again...
...that you won't bow against the power.
So we want to be allies.
Karesi, Candar, Germiyan...
Before the ones who bow
...we need allies who stand strong.
What do you mean by alliance?
-We ll talk.
But you know
...we've come a long way.
As you accepted us as guests here,
...let us have some rest.
You need to rest, huh?
Cerkutay.
My Bey...
-Bey...
Take care of him.
As you order, my Bey.
You didn't share our kimiz.
Let's share your food in the evening then.
So we can keep talking.
Dastard.
Their intention will be revealed soon.
Come on, hatuns.
Come on, sisters.
We need to work faster.
I don't want to cook those vile Mongolians.
Calm down, Ulgen.
Osman Bey is hosting him so we have to.
Ulgen is right. I feel offended too.
Those cruel people shed too much blood.
We'll make them pay for the
blood and the food we offer.
But not now. Now he's a guest here.
Let those vile Mongolians eat rock!
May Allah curse them!
Why do you say so, mother?
My father is a Mongolian too.
My Allah... I didn't mean that!
Ghazi, people like Cerkutay Bey are different.
We curse the cruel ones.
Those carrying stony hearts.
You got it?
You have mercy for everyone.
What about my family?
Why didn't you show mercy for them?
We're going to have hard times.
We'll have to deal with both
heathens and Mongolians.
Heathens can't harm us!
My father will protect us all.
And kill all the heathens.
Take this.
-Bala Hatun?
-Yes.
Did you kill many Byzantines?
The war is to provide justice, girl.
We don't swing our swords to
kill the enemy but provide justice.
But yes, I took many Byzantine lives.
That's what heathens deserve.
They hurt us a lot.
So we loomed over them like thunderbolts!
My girl.
Be careful. Give it to me.
Cerkutay.
Bey, ha?
So you aren't Osman's hand but a
Bey who has a voice in his council, huh?
I'm both his soldier..
...and a Bey of his...
...and one of a thousand
followers fighting for his cause.
Once upon a time
...you were a soldier of Balgay,
the mighty Mongolian commander.
A powerful Mongolian...
...who was bloodthirsty against Turks
and slaughtered men, women and children!
If you walk with a dog, you are a dog.
If you walk with a wolf, you are a wolf.
Thank Allah...
I've found the right path.
I forgot my past.
A bad dog...
...will bring a wolf into the herd.
You were..
...Balgay's bad dog.
But your brother Altuga isn't.
His loyalty to his blood and Khan is
higher than the highest mountains.
Altuga...
Altuga.
They say he is under your command.
Is he in the frontiers with you now?
He is.
He came for you, Cerkutay.
He has a duty.
You two are going to meet soon.
Cerkutay Bey, the tent is ready.
Thank you.
You go have some rest.
Accompany them.
What a nice horse.
Take action immediately, Ilbay.
Here we go.
Byzantine is keeping silent.
But we will stand on alert.
-Increase the number of watchmen.
-As you order, my Shahzade.
Thank you.
Now everybody get to work!
Do I have permission my Shahzade?
Come in.
You wanted to see me, my Shahzade?
Kanyumaz.
Osman Bey...
...accepted your loyalty oath.
Thanks to Allah. May Allah
give Osman Bey a long life.
This is your last chance, Kanyumaz.
Take some lessons from the past.
From now on, Osman Bey's cause is my cause.
I won't disappoint him,
Gonca Hatun. Don't worry.
Get prepared.
We'll go back to the tribe at dawn.
As you order, my Shahzade. As you order.
Gonca.
You look tense.
Is there a problem?
Mongolians.
They've brought blood again,
Alaaddin. Too many died.
Too many families got ruined.
We'll make them pay for
every drop of blood, my hatun.
Don't be upset.
My compassionate hatun..
We'll heal all the wounds
together, Trickster Hatun.
Together, scholar.
Yes.
Take these to our tent.
I'll help. Come on.
Let me help too.
Come on, daughter. Come on.
Throw this into the water wells, Ilbay.
Kayi people will have a
disease that they can never heal.
Osman will be desperate.
As you order, Commander Ulugan.
I will destroy the whole Kayi
tribe without swinging a sword.
Osman will be ruined.
And you'll sit on the chair that belongs to you.
Blood! Blood! Blood!
Hey, man. Stop.
-Thank you, young man.
-I can do it.
Hey, man!
Here.
Stop, man.
I said I'd bring water to
you. Why did you bother?
Thank you.
-Well... I fill, you carry.
-Alright.
Have a nice day, man.
The uninvited will sit on the ground, they say.
But you are a host worthy of his name.
Enjoy it.
Fresh meat.
A bay horse.
A solid sword.
What else a man would want?
Faith and conscience.
Well, of course a human needs these.
But we have another matter now.
You mentioned alliance.
What do you mean by that?
What do you want from me?
A new age is beginning not only in the world
but also in the frontiers you settled in.
You know... Karesi, Candar and all the
beys in the frontiers were subject to us.
All of them except you.
You know my answer.
I'm not here for a loyalty
oath but for alliance.
Although you aren't under our command,
you won't stand against us either.
I told you before.
Turks have no friends but Turks.
Speaking of friends,
...you weren't lucky about Turks either.
Karesi.
Candar, Germiyan...
They weren't soft against you. But
against us Mongolians, they were.
It's the same for Mongolians!
You're divided into a thousand!
From north to south.
From south to east.
You got broken into many khanates.
Now you mention alliance for
those who you couldn't make bow?
Or are you gathering strength for your
Khan to provide the unity of Mongolians?
You're arrogant, Osman.
Do you doubt our strength?
We don't want you to stay
alone in your lands in the frontiers.
And stay without allies.
Besides, you shouldn't
underestimate Olcaytu Khan.
His strength can shake the world.
He's reached the frontiers.
If he reaches out, he can
take any lands he wants.
All the lands and castles.
Karacahisar Castle
Nokers!
Be quiet, hide.
What's happening here?
Come here, open the door.
Nokers, water the stones of Karacahisar...
..with Turkish blood.
They sneaked in!
Genghis Khan...
...before revealing his move to the enemy...
...made his merchants his spies
and sent them upon his enemies.
This is the lineage of Genghis,
my Shahzade. Always the same.
Merchants, the traitors.
They wander around the frontiers freely.
Right.
Right. These Mongols...
...must have already
learned about our precautions.
Surely, they'll look for our weakness.
-Their spies.
-Orhan. Orhan, what happened?
The Mongols have infiltrated the fortress.
-How? How?
From where?
They must have crossed through the tunnels.
Their traitor spies...
...fulfilled their duties.
-Orhan.
They are getting close.
They're coming for you.
Let them come.
Karacahisar will be their grave. Alps...
...position yourselves in the south immediately.
-As you command, my Shahzade.
We'll block their way..
...and trap them inside the fortress.
Boran Bey.
Your path is my path, my Shahzade.
-Let's kill all these dogs.
-Okay.
-Holofira, you stay here.
-No.
If my sword won't be drawn with yours in this
difficult time, then when will it, Orhan?
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate. Come on.
Nokers!
Show the strength of Mongols to Turks!
Spread the flames of fear in their hearts.
Turks..
...believe in Allah.
They seek refuge in Him...
...and fear only Him. You
came here without permission.
Karacahisar..
...will be the grave for you and your dogs.
-Orhan...
..you must be Orhan.
I will hold your leash..
...and make you my dog, Orhan.
-That leash...
...will be your execution rope, dog.
That treacherous Cerkutay...
...hasn't taught you the might...
...and reputation of the Mongols, huh?
What do you even know about
Cerkutay, you son of a dog?
The sword you see here..
...was made by him.
Tell me.
Who are you?
Cerkutay's...
..eternal enemy.
His own brother.
-Altuga.
You are correct, brave boy.
From the barking dog at your gate...
...to the one who dares to say a
thing, I will kill them all with my sword.
-Nokers, attack!
-Alps! Come on!
The southern side has fallen, my Shahzade.
Orhan, Karacahisar is falling,
what are we going to do?
Karacahisar won't fall before I drop my sword!
Alps, retreat inside the fortress!
They're escaping, catch them!
Those who give up easily...
...are those who earn easily.
We suffered so much and made
many sacrifices for these lands.
And if someone...
...is going to set their eyes on them...
...they will have to pay a heavy price.
You face..
...what's written in your destiny.
One day, everyone pays a price.
You hosted us well.
We wish to host you as well.
Where will you host us?
-Is your tent nearby? -No.
We are not around here.
For now.
But those days are not far away.
Commander Ulugan, the
news we awaited has arrived.
You heard, Osman.
Our visit ends here.
Think well on what I've said.
We will meet again.
Don't forget my words.
Ulugan.
Because..
...I always do as I say.
Cerkutay. -My Bey.
Come on.
Accompany them.
As you order, my Bey.
Samil. -My Bey.
Call Ilbay here.
As you order my Bey.
Osman Bey hosted this Mongol, but I am afraid.
Osman Bey does not trust him either.
Let's see what will come out of this visit.
Can I come in, Begum Hatun?
Come in, Ilbay Bey.
-What happened?
-I went to the well...
...and I brought more water.
The water was polluted
during the last sandstorm.
You can now drink clean water.
Thank you.
But..
Do you visit every tent
with that jug in your hand?
Or is this care special to me?
Good night.
What happeend?
Why did Ilbay come here at this hour?
-Nothing important.
He brought water.
Boran Bey, come. Come. Come on Alps!
They are here, Commander Altuga!
Open the door then, what are you waiting for?
Holofira.
Nokers, break the doors!
There is a tunnel behind
the throne. Go through there.
No, no, I won't leave. You
know I won't leave you here.
Holofira. There is no other way. You have to go!
-I won't leave you here!
I will stay here! -Come!
-Orhan! I said no!
-I cannot let you stay here!
Where will you run, Orhan?
Hang on brothers... Come on.
Holofira. Holofira. Don't be scared.
Nothing will happen to me.
-But what if something happens to you?
What am I going to do then?
-Holofira.
I promise you, nothing will happen to me.
You will go and tell my father
everything that happened here. Alright?
This tunnel will lead
you to the Kartalini region.
You'll leave without even looking back.
Come.
My Shahzade, the door will break. Come on!
I will take you, Orhan!
In the name of Allah.
Come, you dastard dogs, come!
I will break your arrogance
courage with my sword, Orhan.
But my sword will get rid of your
courage along with your head.
Your tongue that dares
to speak brave words will...
...beg for mercy when you
fall into my hands, Orhan.
Now it's your turn.
Bring them.
The last two men left in your fortress, Orhan.
You should be thankful, Ulugan wants you alive.
Nokers.
Take their swords.
Ah Cerkutay ah.
Mindless Cerkutay.
Look at the Turks you offered
loyalty after betraying the Mongols.
You will answer for all the innocents
and martyrs who you hurt with your sword!
For all of them!
Nokers, throw these long-tongued,
weak handed men into the dungeon.
Ulugan will take care of them tomorrow.
What?
What do you mean you have a brother, Cerkutay?
Am I not your wife? How
could you hide this from me?
I couldn't tell you, my wife.
I didn't say it...
..to anyone.
How could I know..
...one day they would come to the frontiers?
They came to the frontiers by hurting others.
What is this brother's name?
-Altuga.
-Altuga. Is he your enemy?
In their eyes, I am a traitor.
He must be my enemy.
Can a brother ever be an enemy
to his brother? That's not possible.
You should see him first, then we'll know.
He is not, he cannot be.
You should go and talk to him. What?
I have an uncle?
No!
Father, does he also use double swords?
Does he look like you or me?
Did you start eavesdropping?!
Father, who does he resemble?
Son, it's been a long time. I...
..don't know who he looks like...
Or what kind of person he is..
Is he as strong as you?
Come on! I am hungry!
Come on, look.
Look what I've made for you.
Who should I give the most?
Give it to me. Hatun, give it
to me. Don't let Ghazi grow...
...bigger and stronger. It's
enough for him. Give it to me.
No, mother. I will go to
battle. I will grow. No, father.
Mother, give it to me.
-No. I made a decision.
I work the most in the tribe.
I will eat the most.
-No, I will eat.
-No, mother.
-Give it to me. -No. I will eat.
-Father, I will eat.
No. I will eat. I will eat.
Let go! Dastard demons!
I swear we will make you pay for this!
Let go! Let go!
Shahzade.
You are still talking.
You and Boran are in our hands.
I will destroy each one of you.
You won't be able to do anything.
Just as we killed those
before you, we will send you...
We will send all of you to hell.
We will send you all to hell!
To hell!
If it wasn't for my great commander Ulugan...
..I would kill you know.
But no.
I will make you suffer worse than death, Orhan.
Both you and Boran.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
My Shahzade.
Dastard dog.
Come at me!
Keep hitting!
He came to our tribe, called himself a guest...
...and even offered an alliance, is that so?
Yes.
Right.
We took the head of his envoy.
Yet he still stands before us and play games.
Then...
...what is the actual
purpose of that dog Ulugan?
Could you notice something?
He revealed nothing.
Only...
...one of his soldiers came and said they
received the news they were waiting for.
-Can I come in, my Bey?
-Come in, Ilbay.
My Bey...
...I went after the Mongols as you ordered.
But I lost them after a while.
My Bey...
..couldn't tell anyone but..
..I have a brother.
Altuga.
Do you have a brother?
Yes my Bey...
Uluga
...said that my brother Altuga...
...was on duty at the frontiers.
He was probably the one who sent the news.
But I don't know what they are...
...doing. -We will learn.
We will learn everything. Samil.
Yes my Bey.
Send messengers everywhere...
...to all our properties!
Orhan Bey and Alaeddin Bey will
come back to the tribe immediately.
Send someone to Akhisar.
And you will go to Karacahisar.
As you order, my Bey.
-Mother, father.
-My daughter.
Do you want some water?
Sisters have just brought water from the well.
Yes, give some water, my daughter.
Thank you.
Thank you, my daughter.
Tomorrow we will witness closely what
is happening in Osman's lands. But...
...the thing I don't like about this is...
...wearing stupid Turkmen clothes.
Here.
This is for you.
I will do everything to end Osman and make
Great Rome strong in these lands again.
Once the Mongols attack them...
.we will be there to take action.
Lukas, our soldiers will be ready at all times.
The soldiers have already
taken their positions, Sofia.
There will be nowhere left for Osman to escape.
Well well, Ghazi Bey is also here.
What would our Bey like for
breakfast? I can bring some milk.
Honey and cream? What would you like?
Leave me alone, mother.
I am not feeling well today.
Don't you have anything to do?
Why are you annoying me here?
Go and cook food.
Work with the Sisters. Go on.
I didn't say anything, my Hatun! He did!
He learned all these things from you!
I will kill you now!
I will kill you know! Who...
How dare you talk to your mother like this?
Let me! Annoying you? Did you hear
him? Did you grow up and become a man?
Cerkutay, let go!
I swear, I will break your bones.
Help!
-What's going on?
-Osman Bey!
Osman Bey! Father!
-Father. Father... What happened, girl?
Mongolians attacked Karacahisar.
Orhan... Orhan?
Orhan and Boran Bey stayed to defend the castle.
Orhan sent me here to inform you.
Uluga
This is Ulugan's doing.
He stalled us in the tribe
and then attacked Karacahisar.
Cerkutay, Ilbay! Bring the horses!
My Bey, I'll go with you.
Alaaddin must be on the way.
He will take care of the tribe.
Alright, Bala. Let's go.
Mother. Mother.
No, Holofira. Stand strong.
Orhan will be alright. Don't worry.
Nothing will happen to him.
What's wrong with me?
Boran Bey.
Boran Bey. Boran Bey.
Are you alright, Boran Bey?
Don't worry, my Shahzade.
I'm good enough to beat
those dogs, thank Allah.
When we reach the headquarters,
you won't have no strength left.
You vile dog.
Wolf's sharper look than a sword..
...is enough to spread fear in the
jackal's heart, you Mongolian dog.
Orhan.
This is your lucky day.
Ulugan wants you alive and healthy.
Otherwise...
...I would have taken your eyes out by now.
While you have a chance, you aren't doing it.
But when I get you
...I will make you regret this.
I got your leash, Orhan.
I can tighten it or put it around your neck.
But you will witness.
You will see what happens
to Osman who has established a...
...state with a few alps and
rebelled against Mongolians.
With those a few alps,
...we will break Mongolian dominance...
...and raise our sanjak all around the world!
We'll glorify Allah's name more...
...and bring peace to the whole world.
-Allah is the greatest!
-You're brain dead, Orhan.
Brain dead.
Mongolians will water the lands with blood.
And they will make your people kneel with blood.
I will cut off your wriggling head.
You should know this.
..in these lands which bear fearless men,
...we're never afraid of death.
We bow against nobody.
We seek mercy from nobody.
I will make you seek mercy.
-We will see. -Nokers!
Ulugan is waiting. Take them!
I swear on my name that I
will kill you with your nokers.
Mongolians caught Shahzade Orhan. That's awful!
It's alright, dear. It's alright.
-It's alright, baby.
-Sisters.
How long has it been like this, Fatma?
Everybody got sick at the same time?
Fever, nausea and
stomachache since this morning.
Especially elders and children.
All troubles come one after another!
Everybody got sick here and
Mongolians caught Orhan Bey.
Father will come back with Orhan.
And we'll take care of people
during their absence, right?
Peace be upon you.
Holofira, you are back.
My brother?
What's the matter?
What's wrong with people?
Brother, bad things are happening.
Mongolians attacked Karacahisar.
They caught Orhan and Boran Bey.
We don't know how they are doing.
What are you saying?
Father has gone to Karacahisar.
-He'll come back with Orhan.
-I will go join him.
-Come on.
-Holofira.
Guldane! Guldane!
Help!
-Guldane? Sisters!
-What's going on?
-What's going on here?
-She's not well.
-She has high fever.
-She's burning.
Alps, bring a stretcher!
Take her to the healing
house! Come on, hurry up!
-Come on, help! Hold it!
-Come on.
Come on, come on.
-Careful.
-Come on, take her to the healing house quickly!
-Here we go.
I won't leave you
alone, brother.
Alaaddin, Alaaddin.
Children and elders are falling down one by one.
This looks like a terrible pandemic.
We need you here.
Samil.
-What's the situation?
-It's not good, my Bey.
Mongolians captured the castle.
What about Boran and Orhan?
Going to the castle, we heard from people...
Nokers took Orhan Bey and Boran away.
Ulugan.
What evil are you up to?
Where did they took them?
It's said they took them to the north
but we don't know where, my Bey.
But they said they didn't seem to be well.
Orhan Bey and Boran were being tortured.
Samil.
Go to the south with your alps.
-Saruca and Yusuf. -My Bey. - My Bey.
You go that way.
And we go to the north.
Look everywhere. Come on, my warriors!
-As you order, my Bey.
Bala.
-Are you alright?
-I'm fine, my Bey.
-You're burning. Are you alright?
-It's good.
Fine.
I will destroy the whole Kayi
tribe without swinging a sword.
Osman will be ruined. And you'll
sit on the chair that belongs to you.
Come on. We can't stop
until we take Orhan and Boran.
We will shake the world if we have to.
Come on, warriors!
We've found them, Lukas.
They're outnumbered. It's
time to beat Osman, Sofia.
We'll choke them at their weakest moment.
Lukas.
-Let's go after them.
-Alright.
The flames..
...shall guide you, Ulugan.
Red blood..
...shall give you life, Ulugan.
Your enemies shall vanish, Ulugan!
These lands where we fight,
take lives and shed blood...
...shall glorify us!
May Tengri be our witness!
We'll spread our kin in the whole world!
I've brought you a gift, Ulugan.
Salute Altuga, who is back with victory.
Altuga! Altuga! Altuga!
You poor creatures.
You kneel in front of me miserably.
You can't stand against mighty Mongolians.
I'll take all your cities and lands from you.
I will make you my dogs!
I will take a bath in your blood.
You vile dog.
Untie my hands if you have courage.
Then we will see who can make the other his dog!
Come on! Do you have courage? Untie me!
I will put out your fire, Orhan.
I will destroy your father and Kayi.
My Shahzade!
You dastard. Kill us now..
...or untie our hands.
Let's see who wins.
Ulugan never takes lives without games.
Your torture isn't over yet.
Tie them and take them away.
We ll kill all of you! All
of you! Dog! You vile dog!
You vile dog!
Take care of her.
Let me check. Let me check.
Alaaddin Bey. Yaren..
-Wait, wait.
-Alaaddin Bey.
I'm here.
Help us, my Allah.
Is this a pandemic, Alaaddin Bey?
No.
Not a pandemic.
It's poison.
Everybody is infected at the same time...
Something they eat or drink.
Not everyone cooks the same food.
You're right, Meryem.
Something everybody reaches at the same time.
Water.
Water! Move aside, sister!
Who would poison the well and why?
Vile dogs!
They put poison in the water.
Dastards.
Alps
Examine the water well immediately and clean it!
For now, fetch water from the well in the woods.
Until that water comes
here, nobody will drink water!
Come on.
My Shahzade.
We all drank water from there.
What poison, Alaaddin?
Some poison I have never seen before.
I don't know what it is.
But Mongolians did this.
We need oak bark and
sarsaparilla root immediately.
How can we find
them in this season?
We have to.
We have to. Fatma.
All of you may be poisoned.
Boil yellow centaury and make
everyone drink it. You drink it too.
It will decrease the
poison's effect, God willing.
-We'll do it now, my Bey.
-Good.
-Kanyumaz.
-My Bey.
Demand reinforcements from Sogut immediately.
Alps drank water too. We
shouldn't fall weak here.
As you order, my Bey.
-Gonca, let's go. May Allah protect you.
-Alright.
-Come on.
-I'm going too.
We can find them faster.
Fine. Come on, come on.
You don't look well.
Are you poisoned too?
I'm fine, Meryem.
Don't be afraid. I will be alright.
We need to find clean water. Come on.
Bala Hatun.. Bala?
Bala.
Bala. What's wrong with you?
I don't feel well, Osman.
Something's wrong with
me too. I'm not well, my Bey.
-The same here, my Bey.
-You too?
This is Ulugan's doing.
He must have put poison
in the water in our tribe.
But I don't know how he could do
it while there were so many alps.
Everybody in the tribe got poisoned then.
Alaaddin is there. He will find a cure.
Yes, let's find Orhan first.
Come on!
Osman!
I brought your death to you.
Red demon..
I was waiting for you to come out.
It's time for revenge, Osman.
We have more men than you do.
You will die alone here.
Is that so?
Cerkutay. -My Bey.
We will break through here.
As you order my Bey.
There is still time for these dastards.
We are going to Orhan.
Come on!
Ya Allah!
Soldiers! Run!
Catch them!
Osman would never escape even if
he knew he was going to die, Lukas!
There is something else behind this.
Holy Shaman, what do you see?
I see a gray Sky Wolf.
It has the world in his claw.
Thousands follow him.
They are the descendants of the
ones who melted the iron mountain.
He is a dark man.
Who is he?
Osman!
..Osman does not die..
...he and his descendants...
..will ride horses on three continents
and seven regions. They will spread.
Osman's name will be known everywhere.
Osman's reputation will
be spoken of in the world.
The Sky Wolf is Osman, Ulugan.
As long as...
...I live...
..I will never allow this.
First, I will take his honor...
..then his life.
You will die at my feet, Osman.
Cerkutay. -My Bey.
My Bey
Cerkutay.
Are you alright?
My Bey, they are getting close!
Ilbay.
Take the horses and continue from here.
We need to confuse them.
We will meet in the north.
As you order, my Bey.
Come on, get up.
Let's go.
Come on.
There is no trace anywhere.
What are we going to do now, my Bey?
Wait... Allah is Great.
He will show us a way for sure.
Let's go this way.
Come on.
If the rope that ties my hands...
...was my execution rope,
I would not feel ashamed.
But falling into the hands of these dogs and...
...putting Osman Bey in a difficult situation...
Now is not the time for shame..
...but the time to rise and ruin
the games of these dastard dogs.
Okay my Shahzade.
We will escape from here.
My Shahzade. -Tell me.
There is a dagger in my boot.
But I cannot find a chance
to reach and take it. But...
...they have defenses here
that is like an eagle's nest.
You...
..stretch out your boot.
Eagles do not fit in cages...
..lions...
...do not fit in forests, Boran Bey.
What are you doing there?
What is in your hand?
In my hand..
...in my hand...
...is your death.
My Shahzade, I will distract them, you leave!
We either leave together, or
we die together, Boran Bey.
My Shahzade.
Come on, come on.
So you are running, dogs.
You are trying to escape but
no one escapes from Ulugan.
Orhan.
If you have the courage..
...if you trust your strength, face me.
Come and I will take that dirty head of yours.
Step aside.
Altuga.
Bring them here.
I will show them what pain is.
You and I will meet again Orhan.
You are lucky today, Altuga.
You are lucky today.
Bring them.
God..
Protect him...
Do not take him from me.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Allah is sufficient for us.
You protected him before.
Now I am asking You with his heart.
I am begging You with his words.
Please, protect him.
My Bey, what did these dastards make us drink?
We are slowly losing our strength.
I don't know what made us drink...
...but once its effect disappears...
...we know what to do to them.
My Bey. My Bey.
My Bey.
I tried hard, but I couldn't succeed.
They are everywhere. They are coming here.
I can smell you, Osman.
The red devil is here.
Come here.
Come here, come here.
Come face me.
Let's end this today, Osman.
Where are you?
My Bey, don't. Please don't.
My Bey, we shouldn't face them in this state.
Cerkutay.
Are you alright?
I am.
You are not.
You are worried about Orhan.
Do you think I can't see it?
You are trying to stand tall, I know.
But your heart is in pain, I'm aware.
I cannot fall, Gonca.
I cannot show my pain to
anyone who cannot heal it.
Holofira.
No matter what we went through...
No matter what..
You are not alone in this situation.
If you get tired, I will help you.
And when you gain your strength again...
...if you want to see me against you again...
...don't worry.
I'll stand against you.
Then we can fight.
No. No! It's no where!
It's not here!
What are we going to do Alaeddin?
Let's go that side.
We don't have much time, come on.
Come on.
We never bow down to..
...the dishonest ones!
Do your best, you dog!
Dastard dogs!
You don't know Ulugan yet.
You will experience pain now.
The most valuable trait of the
Alps is the hands that hold swords.
If you can't hold a sword, you'll die, Orhan.
You'll die.
Watch, you dog.
Altuga.
My Shahzade.
Kayis could not hear you, Orhan!
Louder!
Has your fire gone out, Orhan?
Has your tail, held high, now bent?
If you try to escape again,
I'll nail your other hand too.
I told you, you'll be a dog at my door.
No one escapes from Ulugan.
Your greatest regret in this
life will be not killing me, dog
Not killing me!
Crush the miserable Boran.
Bury him in the ground.
Come, come, you dog's children, come.
I swear, Ulugan!
I swear, I will take your life! I swear!
I found you, Osman.
Who dares attack the
commander and soldiers of Rome?
Holy Ulugan calls you. You will come with me.
The infidels are uniting again.
But we know how to defeat them.
Get lost Mongol.
Osman is in my hands, I will kill him.
I will not repeat it, Hatun.
You will either listen to me, or...
I hope Ulugan has a good thing to give to us...
Or else, it will be really, really bad.
We are leaving.
My Bey, what are we going to do now?
You will follow them. We will find Ulugan's
place. That's what matters the most for us.
As you order, my Bey.
Bala.
Alaeddin.
Alaeddin, is it this one?
No. Not this one. -What about this?
It looks like this one.
But this is not what we need either.
But I guess we are close.
We will search thoroughly. Come on. Come on.
Hamza Alp.
What are you doing here?
Alaeddin Bey, I lost my mother.
I came to do whatever I can
so other families will not suffer.
May Allah have mercy on her.
Yeter Mother was a mother to
all of us. I'm sorry for your loss.
But..
...I know that as long as
she has a son like you...
...her deed book will always be open...
...and it will be filled with
good deeds, God willing.
God willing.
Come on then.
Help us. -As you order my Shahzade.
-Come on.
Alaeddin.
I found it! -Yes!
This is the one!
Thanks to Allah!
Cannibal dogs!
Gonca, Holofira. Are you alright?
-Yes. Are you?
-Thanks to Allah, I'm good.
But there is no sarsaparilla here.
We're running out of time.
Let's pick these roots.
-I'll try to make antidote with them.
-Let's go.
Come on.
Hold on. Obviously, his
intention isn't to kill us...
...but make us live.
He's playing with us, Osman.
-My Bey.
-Cerkutay.
My Bey, they are moving too fast.
We lost the trails.
We will find them, my Bey. Let's keep going.
Bala. Bala.
I feel cold, Osman.
This...
What is this? Poison's effect..
...is getting stronger.
We can't do this here.
Cerkutay, find somewhere to have rest.
-Come on.
-Okay, my Bey.
So we can also hunt and regain strength.
Come on.
Bala.
Hold on, my gazelle-eyed woman.
As you're here with me, I will hold on.
Yes, I'm here for you.
I'm here.
Sister Ulgen!
-Sister Ulgen, Ghazi got sick!
-Ghazi!
-Come.
-Mother.
Sit here. Give him some tea! Sister!
Give it to me. Drink this, my dear.
Meryem.
Meryem isn't here.
I'll go find Meryem.
Ulgen.
Fatma Hatun.
You don't look well. Sit down.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'll go find Meryem.
Jesus Christ.
I didn't avenge my parents.
Don't let me die.
The poor seeks help.
Give me strength.
Mother.
Where are you?
Why don't you come, mother?
Meryem.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
-Come.
-I will be alright.
Before I avenge my parents
..I won't die.
We boiled some centaury.
Come on.
You need to drink some, alright?
Let's go.
Fatma.
You are burning. You're burning.
I need to bring help.
Should I help you, Fatma?
He took Orhan captive, huh?
That means, Sofia
...that he is our ally.
Ulugan waits.
As I was so close to kill Osman,
...you brought us here.
I never share my preys.
And only I decide who dies here.
By looking at my clothes, don't confuse
me with those ordinary tribe beys, Ulugan.
You're talking to the commander of Rome.
What did you do to Osman?
He could barely walk.
You're a smart woman.
You know well what to ask.
Your eyes..
Your look..
...is like poison.
And I like poison.
I put poison all the wells in their tribe.
Poena..
My little vengeance angel.
Don't die, my little baby.
I hope you didn't drink the water.
Sofia.
What poison is it?
Is there an antidote?
It seems there is someone
precious to you in the tribe.
Give me the antidote, Ulugan.
To demand something from me,
you should do something I want first.
What do you want?
Help us, my Allah.
Come on, come on.
Gonca, Holofira.
Mash them quickly and boil.
If we do it together, it'll
be enough for everyone.
Come on, sisters! Come on!
Come here, my dear. You will be alright.
I will heal you. Don't worry.
-Alaaddin Bey. Alaaddin Bey.
-Meryem.
Alaaddin Bey, you should help.
-Fatma Hatun blacked out. What?
Take her to the healing house.
Take me to my sister.
-In my tent.
-Your tent? That one?
-You go check her.
-Fatma!
Fatma... Fatma,
you will be alright.
You will be alright, my
beautiful sister. My dear sister...
My dear...
Come on, alps!
I'm not helpless.
I'm on my own..
..but not helpless.
Meryem, Meryem.
You aren't well either.
Let's go to the healing house.
Let's go, Meryem.
You're being stubborn but you aren't well.
Help us, my Allah. Help us.
Bala.
-Bala.
-Osman.
You're burning in fever.
You're burning.
Open your mouth.
Take this. This will be good for you.
This..
...will decrease the poison's effect.
Osman.
How are people in the tribe doing?
Don't worry. Alaaddin
will definitely find the cure.
And we will endure, Bala.
For our children.
Look at me. When I see you like this,
...I remember the times you were sick.
You slept all the time first but then..
Look. I'm a strong woman, Brunet Osman.
A hatun walking in your
path won't fall down easily.
Of course, you are strong.
Behind every strong woman, there is a mountain.
I am your mountain.
I will never let anything happen to you.
Well... I'm getting better now.
But..
Orhan..
Knowing the enemy caught him...
..makes my heart ache.
Don't worry. Orhan is strong.
He has my blood. He won't die easily.
Besides, they have to kill me first.
Don't worry. We will beat this poison.
We will beat the enemy as well.
God willing.
I will fight to my last breath for
us, our children and our state!
You will see.
Come on. Get some sleep. You should rest.
My beautiful sister.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
O Healer! O Healer! O Healer!
Heal her, my Allah.
Many have died since the morning.
All those children..
What if this cure doesn't work?
I will figure something out, Ulgen Hatun.
Guldane, drink some.
I am...
What?
I did terrible things to you.
What do you mean, Guldane?
Begum... Begum Hatun..
...wanted to turn you two...
...against...
..each other.
I've brought clean water.
Don't tire yourself anymore.
We heard what you said.
Is she alright?
The medicine didn't heal anyone.
Alaaddin.
They are getting worse. What now?
We couldn't find sarsaparilla roots.
I thought this would decrease
the poison's effect, but it didn't.
It didn't.
Guldane.
Guldane! Guldane!
-My friend died!
-Wait, Begum Hatun.
She drank the medicine you made but she died.
-There is no cure for this?
-I will find. I will.
I will find the antidote whatever it takes!
Orhan.
Any news from Orhan, Osman?
Any news from Orhan?
Sleep, sleep. You should sleep.
Sleep.
My Allah.
Don't test me with my children, my Allah.
Please protect them.
It's You who gives and takes, my Allah.
You trusted us for them, my
Allah. Let me protect them.
My Halime... My precious...
I couldn't protect Halime.
Please protect my children, my Allah.
My Hatun, let me carry her.
Don't come, Osman.
Don't come.
Don't say that, Bala. No.
My daughter...
Look. Your father is here.
Wake up.
Wake up and hug your father.
Play games with him.
Come on.
Come on, my daughter.
Bala... No.
Halime...
Don't upset your father.
Don't look, Osman Bey.
It's been ten days since
she fell into the river.
No.
"To Allah we belong and to Him we will return."
My daughter...
Halime...
Osman..
I couldn't protect her...
I couldn't protect her Osman... I left her...
I left her there..
I couldn't hold her hand!
I left her there!
I couldn't protect my daughter!
I couldn't protect my child
I left her...
I left her there!
Can I come in, my Bey?
Cerkutay... Come in, Cerkutay!
Ilbay found the tracks, my Bey.
Good, then...
We'll perform our morning prayer and leave.
Thanks to Allah.
Bala, you go to the tribe now.
We don't know what our children are doing.
As you order, my Bey. -My Bey...
You are not alright..
Orhan and Boran..
We will save them.
As you order my Bey.
No, my Bey! No!
The tracks disappear after a point!
What?
We won't stop.
We'll keep looking. Until we find Orhan...
...we will not stop. Come on.
My Bey.. My Bey...
The poison flows in our blood.
At least you should go to the
tribe, and I'll keep searching.
What are you saying? No.
This is the rope that
will pull you into the well.
My Bey.
There are tracks here!
Let me go.
Dastard dogs.
They covered it with leaves.
Tracks go this way.
Dastard dog.
This way.
Come on.
Commander Ulugan.
Is the trap that will bring Osman to us ready?
-It is ready, commander.
-Is the bait ready?
It's ready too, commander.
Come Osman.
Spread your wings and come to your death.
Mother...
Is there news from Orhan?
We found their tracks, they
are after them my daughter.
God willing they will find him.
-God willing.
Are you alright?
What... what happened here?
Mother, they poisoned the water.
Alaeddin is searching for the
antidote, but he hasn't found it yet.
What about you and Osman Bey? Are you alright?
You drank the water too.
-We are alright.
Where is Fatma?
Fatma is poisoned, mother.
We took her to the tent.
You take care of our people,
I will go and check Fatma.
Meryem?
-She is with Fatma. -Good.
Mother...
Let me go...
Mother.
Mother..
Mother...
My Fatma!
Mother..
My daughter?
My daughter!
My Bey, are you alright?
-I am, I am alright, Cerkutay.
What is the situation?
These nokers are positioned on
the right side of this den of dogs.
They are all waiting around
that Ulugan dog's tent.
Orhan and Boran?
My Bey.
What's the situation on the left side, Ilbay?
My Bey, I saw them.
They are there, in the headquarters.
What about the nokers?
My Bey, there are patrolling soldiers.
But the measures are not strict.
Apparently, they think we won't find them.
Go ahead.
They are there, my Bey.
Ilbay, you will go from the left.
Cerkutay, you from the
right. Handle the guard too.
As you order my Bey.
Orhan.
Boran, brother! I am here brother!
My Bey... -Boran
My Bey...
We are trapped.
My Bey.
Welcome Osman..
Dastard dog..
Faithless dog...
You came for your son and your
Alp, but you are at the end of the road.